<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Database Project</string>


    <!-- The BMI Text -->
    <string name="bmiTitle">BMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="bmiHeight">My Height is ...</string>
    <string name="bmiWeight">My Weight is ...</string>
    <string name="bmiBtnTitle">My BMI is ...</string>

    <!-- Country Name -->
    <string-array name="countryname">
        <item>Bangladesh</item>
        <item>India</item>
        <item>Malaysia</item>
        <item>Dubai</item>
        <item>Japan</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="info1">Assalamualaikum.\nThis is Tanjil Alom. My ID is 201-15-3079. This is my project for Android Development Course.</string>


    <string name="bd">Bangladesh, to the east of India on the Bay of Bengal, is a South Asian country marked by lush greenery and many waterways.
        Its Padma (Ganges), Meghna and Jamuna rivers create fertile plains, and travel by boat is common.
        On the southern coast, the Sundarbans, an enormous mangrove forest shared with Eastern India, is home to the royal Bengal tiger.</string>

    <string name="malaysia">Malaysia is a Southeast Asian country occupying parts of the Malay Peninsula and the island of Borneo.
        It\'s known for its beaches, rainforests and mix of Malay, Chinese, Indian and European cultural influences.
        The capital, Kuala Lumpur, is home to colonial buildings, busy shopping districts such as Bukit Bintang and skyscrapers such as the iconic, 451m-tall Petronas Twin Towers.</string>

    <string name="india">India, officially the Republic of India, is a country in South Asia. It is the seventh-largest country by area,
        the second-most populous country, and the most populous democracy in the world. New Delhi is the capital of India. </string>

    <string name="japan">Japan is an island country in East Asia. It is situated in the northwest Pacific Ocean,
        and is bordered on the west by the Sea of Japan, while extending from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north toward the East China Sea,
        Philippine Sea, and Taiwan in the south.</string>

    <string name="dubai">Dubai is a city and emirate in the United Arab Emirates known for luxury shopping,
        ultramodern architecture and a lively nightlife scene. Burj Khalifa, an 830m-tall tower, dominates the skyscraper-filled skyline.
        At its foot lies Dubai Fountain, with jets and lights choreographed to music. On artificial islands just offshore is Atlantis,
        The Palm, a resort with water and marine-animal parks. </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>